This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander!
A hero!
This is my story!
Thank
you.
I've never seen my
dreams It's not too high,
it's not too high
It's not too high,
it's not too high I wanted to do
that When you were in the moment,
I was connected to myself
I'll be back in my way,
I'll be back in my way
I'll be back here
I'll be back in the edge
of this world I will
be back in my future
We'll be back together
you want to keep yuki yes i would
like him for the sixth quadrant i've
excelled at academics ever since i was
young and my rank reflects that things
have been smooth sailing but you might
say my personal life is a bit dull
i'm in need of a little pet i want
someone i can come home too and bring
some much-needed joy if you're willing
to be flexible and handsome over
I would be willing to endorse you as
the next supreme
commander I'm going
to become supreme commander on my
own not by leveraging my inferiors oh
dear is our meeting over what about
fading the little slave in my free time.
Huh?
Miss Tenka said that she wants me? Yep.
Seems she's looking for a companion.
A companion?
So she wants a pet.
Yeah, that's exactly
how she put it. A pet?
But I'm...
I'm busy being the 7th
Squadron's caretaker. Good.
I'm glad you said that.
The 7th Squadron does need you.
But like I told Tenka, I have no
control over your personal life right?
The problem is I don't really
have a whole lot of free time?
Did you lose weight?
I'm
exhausted.
Ms.
Tenka, huh.
It feels good that a gorgeous woman
like her would want me, but...
I'm supposed to be a hero, not a pet.
Hi. Ms. Tenka!
I snuck away to come see you.
For a personal visit.
As in...
Kyo told you, didn't she?
That I have a crush on you.
I was hoping you might like to be
my boyfriend. Be your boyfriend?
Not a lackey or a pet?
No, a relationship.
I just called you a pet
because you're so adorable.
The slave devoted to his master.
Your bravery won me over.
And let's not forget your
impressive housekeeping skills.
Right now I see you as more of a
pet because you're young and cute.
But if you grow up to be big and strong,
I might spoil you.
My heart won't stop racing.
I've never felt anything like this before.
I had wanted to do this the right way.
But I doubt I can resist you any longer.
What do you mean?
Just relax.
I'm just going to take off your clothes.
I cannot relax!
Speaking of which, is the shirt you're
wearing important to you? Huh? No!
It's just a cheap old t-shirt I picked up!
Whoa!
That's abusing your ability!
Now, can't you at least tell me
whether you'll go out with me or not?
One, I accept your proposal.
Two, I need time to mull it over.
I'm going with option
two! Final answer! I see.
It was a bit too sudden.
But it's not necessarily a no.
Which makes me think I should do
something to keep you from slipping.
Yuki!
Let's play video games!
You pounced on him out of
nowhere when did you get so
aggressive i must have been
under the Little slave spell how
indecent i know i said that
i wouldn't interfere in your
personal life but Oh oh pick
me sneaking into another dorm
in the middle of the night
is inconsiderate regardless
Of circumstance it's immoral
behavior and we should never
abuse our abilities there you
have It point taken you're
dismissed go home already sure
catch you later little slave
I'm worn out early morning
practice tomorrow Do not be late.
Right!
Lend it out?
Today, in preparation for our
battle against the humanoid Shuki,
I'd like to try lending my slave ability.
It would enable you two to
utilize Yuki when in slave form.
It's my guess that his attributes
change based on the person riding him.
That's right.
He didn't look the same when I wrote him.
And depending on those attributes,
it would expand the list of strategic
tools available to us. Makes sense.
Combining our abilities with the
Commander sounds like a lot of fun!
You're up first, Nei.
Give it a shot. Great!
Is it okay if I step on
your back? Of course.
Don't worry about it.
Nay, take hold of the chains.
Another form that's
different from Himari's!
This might actually work! Agreed.
What do you think, Yuki?
How is Nei's version?
I'd have to move around first.
Hey, Nei, can I test it out?
Do what you need to.
I'm holding on tight.
I don't feel as strong.
And you move a lot slower
than in Whirlwind mode.
But on the other hand, my
senses feel sharper than ever.
My eyesight and my hearing.
Oh, I see.
Like for scouting.
If I use my brand break trick and channel
energy into my eyes, I can probably...
Huh?
I'M SEEING SOMETHING I REALLY SHOULDN'T!
I'M SO SORRY!
So you can see through our clothes?
Now I can see your backside!
Mistake, you can just
face the other direction!
Good idea! You're smart, Nate!
Sure vision.
That means it enhanced his eyesight.
An attribute like that could be
used to sniff out hidden Shuki.
However, it takes a heavy toll.
Unlike Himari's learning,
lending my ability sucks a
considerable amount of my strength.
Huh?
What was that?
Well done, Mr. Yuki!
Oh, no! I'm sorry!
I don't understand!
My body started moving on its own!
I apologize!
Please! It's fine!
Don't worry about it!
So the one responsible for paying an equal
price is the borrower, not the lender.
Forgive me.
I assumed I would be in charge of his
compensation while lending my ability.
It's fine!
Oh, I get it!
Ahem! Ahem! Ahem!
Now it's my turn!
Let's see what Yuki's form is with me!
Are you positive?
It's very likely you'll engage in battle.
In a full-blown fight,
your reward may end up being
much more extreme than Ney's was.
Extreme?
Well, well.
Time for your hard-earned reward.
Is this the kind of thing you like?
You're such a naughty boy, Yuki.
Ready when you are.
Sure you can handle it? I'll be fine!
Ridding Shuki is the
Demon Defense Forces job!
A silly reward won't stop me!
Good answer. Hop on. Right!
And Shushu Sunuga takes the reins!
That was cool!
She looks very excited!
Come on, Yuki!
Let's give you some Shushu flair!
Oh, yeah!
I feel insanely strong, but
also more sluggish than before.
You look bulkier, too.
I'll admit that he's powerful,
but it's not worth lending my
ability for a simple upgrade.
Hold on a sec!
Let's not be hasty!
If I turn myself huge,
there's a pretty good chance that
Yuki would get bigger along with me!
Wait, is that true?
Heroes are always working out, right?
Just to have a little faith.
All right!
Paradigm shift!
And here's your reward.
I'm sorry, Shushu.
It looks like we won't be using
your version in combat. I know.
Um, Miss Kyoka, will you be okay?
Yes.
Although I will need to
get used to it as well.
For the time, we'll prioritize your
skills with Nei as your writer.
Okay.
Nei, time to go. That's right!
I need to get ready for school!
Come to think of it,
I wonder why Nei joined the Demon
Defense Force in the first place.
Okay, I'm off!
Okay, be careful. Great!
Miss Kyouka, would it be alright
if I walked Nei to school today?
I'd like to talk to her a bit.
I'll allow it.
She's your superior, so it's
best that you get to know her.
Sorry, I know you're busy.
Oh, don't worry about me.
I'll get my work done.
so you would like to know why i joined
yeah it's just it must be tough going to
school and working for the demon defense
force not having school every day does help
plus the demon defense force is a great
cause since i might end
up finding my parents?
Some time ago, out of the blue,
while Nei's mother and father went missing,
all signs pointed to a motto mishap.
You lost family, too.
Mr.
Yuki, you've heard the rumors
floating around, haven't you?
About people receiving phone
calls from their relatives,
who vanished in mishaps, or
catching glimpses of them.
I hear stories like that sometimes.
So, you joined the Demon
Defense Force because...
When I ate a peach and
gained my clairvoyant powers,
I think Ney's feelings
manifested as her ability.
I see.
Hence the name of your ability.
Promise!
Sure to find!
Hmm.
I'm sure they're alive.
Just like I believe my big
sister's still out there. Yeah.
A message from the Supreme Commander? Yep.
If we locate the humanoid Shuki,
we aren't to engage with them
until she gives the order.
It seems like her goal is to create
a dialogue with the humanoids.
I think she wants to assess
how intelligent they are.
They're the type to attack
first and ask questions never.
If all goes well, she believes we
could reveal the mysteries of Mato,
solve the Shuki problem,
and prevent Mato mishaps.
Wishful thinking at best.
I intend to gather all
commanders for meetings soon.
Please present your opinion then.
I highly doubt the Shuki are
going to respond to his summons.
I know, right?
It would probably devolve
into a battle anyway.
The sixth squad devotes its complete
cooperation to the seventh squadron.
Sounds good to me.
We're home.
Hi.
Welcome back, guys.
Sorry, but can you grab
some water for Tenka? Sure.
Sorry about that.
I didn't mean to tease you.
It's fine.
Tenka, you're not drunk, are you?
Shall we test that theory?
By doing what, exactly? Oh, no.
Nei has a strong feeling
she shouldn't watch this.
Yuki...
We've spotted the appearance
of numerous gateways.
Coordinates confirmed.
Help is on the way. Sounds good.
We're heading out.
Let's move. Roger.
I'll drop you off.
Thank you.
Commander!
And Miss Tenka?
Shall I stay in assist? No.
This area is under our jurisdiction.
We'll handle the situation.
Bye. Good luck.
Thank you, Miss Tenka. Let's move. Right.
It kind of seems like Miss
Kyoka's in a bad mood.
Listen, I know I said that I wouldn't
interfere in your personal life,
but I'm taking it back.
There will be no more fawning over another
squad's commander at the end of the day.
You are my slave.
Got it.
Looks like you're in need of
harsher disciplinary methods?
Let's beat the shit out of them!
Roger!
Oh, wow!
Gotcha! A new type!
Huh.
You don't see that every day.
It's tough!
And it regenerates quickly.
Let's finish this! Right!
It's time to bow down!
Mighty Blade Cross!
Oh no, they got a minster kill.
Augmented Shuuki.
Are good in theory, but
not so good in practice.
What are you up to?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm just trying to have a little fun.
Humans like combining and
modifying stuff too, don't they?
But I guess having that level of
durability is basically useless.
I'll never understand what's
going on in that head of yours.
Now what do you think I should try next?
It's over.
After I transformed,
The things you said to me!
Hype me up!
Oh yeah?
Hmm.
Little slave.
You truly are a slave
at heart, aren't you?
It only makes me want you more.
I don't think my personal life is
going to be as tall from now on
Thank you.
Thank you
very
much.
I won't let you go.
I won't let you
go.
She's from Shimane Prefecture
and her hobbies include...
We're running out of time, so
next time, Reunion Coco Lick!